From warrior I, we're going to continue through the sun salutation.
So we're in warrior I; the inhale is going to be to invite both palms to the earth, and the exhale is going to invite the left foot back into plank; high plank.
Now we're looking to have the hips directly in line with the shoulders.
Oftentimes, people need to lift their hips, because they just don't have the core stability.
We can do this here, lengthening out the crown of your head; draw from the front of your body, top of the pubis, right through the sternum, right through, draw that in for strength.
The next thing that you're able to do is release the knees.
This is going to make the pose more available to you.
She still needs to lengthen through the crown of her head.
And if it's still too much work for the lower back, for the abs, she's going to walk her knees in even closer, coming into table, but still have some work going on in the shoulders.
She's still asking the core of her body to do some work.